rummypassion.com 2018-10-03

# Privacy Policy of Rummy Passion | Indian Rummy

## Rummy Player Privacy

This privacy policy is a part of the RummyPassion.com website's [Terms of Use](https://www.rummypassion.com/terms-of-use "Term of Use").

RummyPassion.com offers skill based games like online Rummy in a safe, secure, dependable and comfortable environment. These games are fun to play and participate in and knowing there is trustworthy management behind RummyPassion.com should give you the player, peace of mind. We are completely dedicated to protecting the privacy of our players.

This document describes what information we collect from our players and how we use the information. Potential players and users must register with us to access and play our games. We collect certain information about you during the registration process and before processing any financial transactions. This information includes your name, email id, mobile number, postal address etc. Provision of this information is mandatory by you if you want to access our Products and/ or Services. By registering on the Rummypassion.com website, you automatically permit for your personal information to be used as stated in this privacy policy. We also collect your IP address information in addition to your personal information when you visit our website. IP addresses of our players help us to study user behaviour, research demographics of our users and provide improvements to our users as a result of this collective information. Rummypassion.com is the exclusive user of this information collected on its website and will not share, sell, rent this information in ways other than what is described in this document. We may be required by law to disclose information at times.

Rummypassion.com does not divulge your personal information to a third party without your consent. We use your personal information to better your user experience and to present our players with new offers, products and services. We may share your personal information with prize sponsors and delivery agents through our site.

Rummypassion.com employs stringent security measures to avoid loss and misuse of information you provide us. Your personal details are password protected and only you can access your information. Rummypassion.com is not responsible or liable for any activity which is undertaken when your password is used. For this we advise you not to reveal your password to anyone.

You agree to provide us personal information about yourself when you accept Terms of Use and Privacy Policy on the registration page. In case you do not wish to share this information with us, please do not register on the RummyPassion.com website. Remember, our registration procedure requires you to provide us with this information. If you wish to play cash games or participate in tournaments, competitions, contests or other marketing activity that we initiate, you will be asked to provide us additional information.

## Our Policy on Children

RummyPassion.com is vehemently dedicated to protecting the privacy of children and does not intentionally collect or use personal details of children under the age of 13. We are in full compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). If someone wrongfully or inadvertently provides personal details of children under the age of 13, RummyPassion.com will securely delete this information from its records and will bar that individual from accessing its products and or services.

## Use of Cookies and Pixel Tags

RummyPassion.com employs certain technology and cookies to collect and store certain information every time you access the website. Cookies make it possible for this website to identify the information you have agreed to provide to this website. This aggregated information assists us in establishing and analyzing the most usable parts of our website. Rummypassion.com may also employ cookies to show you advertising. These advertisements may be displayed by us or for us by a third party.

You may change your computer’s settings to disallow your browser to accept cookies.

RummyPassion.com employs third parties to advertise on our behalf on our site as well as other websites. These third parties collect details about your browsing habits and your visits to our website including details on your behaviour with our products and or services. They may utilise this collective information about on-site activity and off-site activity to place advertisements. This information is collected with the help of pixel tag technology, the use of which is very common on most prevalent websites on the internet. This collected information remains anonymous.

## Rummy Player Consent

When you access our website, you give your consent to the collection and use of this information by Rummypassion.com, its partners and affiliates. From time to time, we may change our methods of collecting information and modify our privacy policy. We will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

If and when you do not wish to receive e-mail or sms notifications and other marketing details from us, or you wish to remove browsing details that we have collected about you, please you may change your preferences in  My Account section.
